{
    "subject": "resource/Death_Angel",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Musical_groups_from_the_San_Francisco_Bay_Area",
    "human_readable": "Death Angel is a musical group from the San Francisco Bay Area.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8175577521324158,
            "question": "Is Death Angel a local band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7690353393554688,
            "question": "What type of group is Death Angel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712225615978241,
            "question": "Where is Death Angel from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5788894891738892,
            "question": "What are some popular music genres from the San Francisco Bay Area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5431084632873535,
            "question": "Are there any famous musicians from the San Francisco Bay Area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237266421318054,
            "question": "What is Death Angel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47044217586517334,
            "question": "Where did Death Angel originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45972493290901184,
            "question": "What is the music scene like in the San Francisco Bay Area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23788993060588837,
            "question": "Does Death Angel have a large fan base?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1677045077085495,
            "question": "Has Death Angel won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Death Angel is a musical group from the San Francisco Bay Area.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2247_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Death Angel have a large fan base?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2247_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the music scene like in the San Francisco Bay Area?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2247_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Death Angel originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2247_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2247_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Death Angel is a musical group from the San Francisco Bay Area.\" Multiple sources confirm that Death Angel was formed in San Francisco's famous Bay Area and are part of the Bay Area thrash metal scene."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}